<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Monster Job Search Results big_data</title>
    <description>RSS Feed for Monster Job Search</description>
    <link>http://rss.jobsearch.monster.com/rssquery.ashx?q=big_data</link>
    <image>
      <title>Monster Job Search Results big_data</title>
      <url>http://media.monster.com/mm/usen/my/144x30_monsterBug.gif</url>
      <link>http://rss.jobsearch.monster.com/rssquery.ashx?q=big_data</link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>30</height>
    </image>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Monster. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <webMaster>RssJobSearch@monster.com</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 12:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
    <docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss</docs>
    <generator>RSS.NET: http://www.rssdotnet.com/</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data - Engineer/Elastic Administrator</title>
      <description>VA-Sterling, Big Data Engineer / Elastic Administrator Memphis, TN or Sterling VA (Remote) MUST: Must be eligible for a Public Trust Experienced Big Data Engineer / Elastic Administrator 5+ years hands-on experience with supporting Linux production environments 2+ years hands-on experience with supporting Elasticsearch in production Proven track record with Red Hat Enterprise Linux administration Unix/Linux ad</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Engineer-Elastic-Administrator-Job-Sterling-VA-US-222109512.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222109512</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:31:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Solution Architect</title>
      <description>WA-Redmond, Development of solutions / proposals for implementation and design of scalable big data architecture Participation in consulting assessments to understand current state architecture, map it to business priorities, identify gaps and recommend a big data solutions architecture Participation in customer’s workshops and presentation of the proposed solution Design, implement and deploy high-performanc</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Solution-Architect-Job-Redmond-WA-US-221738485.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221738485</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 01:15:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data (Hadoop) Developer</title>
      <description>NJ-Newark, Big Data (Hadoop) Developer Location: Newark, NJ Duration: 6+ month contract to hire Interview process: Phone and WebEx Req. # 20-01275 Contact: Brian Anderson D. 952-562-4101 Our client has an opening for a Data Engineer/Data Wrangler who will be responsible for delivering data on-prem and Cloud applications. The ideal candidate would be responsible for developing and delivering Data Lake solutio</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Hadoop-Developer-Job-Newark-NJ-US-221298397.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221298397</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Architect</title>
      <description>NC-Charlotte, Immediate need for a Big Data Architect for our client in the Financial Services Industry. This is a 12 month contract opportunity with long-term potential and is located in Charlotte, NC. Please review the below job description and contact me ASAP. Looking for Big Data Platform Architect to be a part of the development of next-generation enterprise big data platform that supports every line of bu</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Architect-Job-Charlotte-NC-US-221725794.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221725794</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:10:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Data Engineer / Azure Consultant / Big Data Engineer / Data Engineer :: Remote Work/Dallas, TX</title>
      <description>TX-Richardson, Job Details: Title – Azure Data Engineer / Azure Consultant / Big Data Engineer/Data Engineer Location – Remote Work / Dallas TX After COVID Situation Duration – 12+ Months / Long Term Position Job Description: Should have extensive experience in Azure Databricks, Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 (ADLS GEN2), Databricks-Delta Lake, Azure Data Factory etc. Should have experience in larger Hadoop Eco Sy</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Azure-Data-Engineer-Azure-Consultant-Big-Data-Engineer-Data-Engineer-Remote-Work-Dallas-TX-Job-Richardson-TX-US-220924388.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">220924388</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 18:23:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lead Developer (Java, Spring boot, Big Data) PEDS Eden Prairie, MN UHGJP00060896 - B</title>
      <description>MN-Eden Prairie, job summary: •Performing all phases of software engineering including requirements analysis, application design, and code development &amp; testing •Designing and implementing product features in collaboration with business and IT stakeholders •Design, develop and test reusable frameworks, libraries and Java components •Work with other engineers and teams to create and maintain dev-ops processes, appl</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Lead-Developer-Java-Spring-boot-Big-Data-PEDS-Eden-Prairie-MN-UHGJP00060896-B-Job-Eden-Prairie-MN-US-222099536.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222099536</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 17:27:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Developer - Advanced</title>
      <description>CA-San Francisco, Principal duties/Roles and responsibilities: Big Data Engineer Location: Remote is ok during this pandemic situation. Preferred SF Bay area candidate. We will add more locations as required. Duration: 12-18 months The client is looking for a Big Data Engineer to join the Advanced Data and Analytics Capabilities Team. We are a team-based out of San Francisco that partners with business lines across</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Developer-Advanced-Job-San-Francisco-CA-US-222095030.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222095030</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 14:48:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Engineer - AWS</title>
      <description>VA-Herndon, Big Data Engineer - AWS Job Number: 20-07638 Find your next opportunity in Financial Services! Eclaro is looking for a Big Data Engineer - AWS for our client in Herndon, VA. Eclaro’s client is a leading housing lender, providing financing for private and commercial for many Americans. If you’re up to the challenge, then take a chance at this rewarding opportunity! Position Overview: Use modern too</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Engineer-AWS-Job-Herndon-VA-US-222093836.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222093836</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data/ Hadoop Engineer</title>
      <description>MO, About Us: SynergisticIT is a full service staffing and placement firm servicing client in Northern America and Canada for the past 10 years. We are dedicated towards fulfilling the IT needs of our clients. From staffing to full implementation of projects we provide the highest quality IT Services. We do provide skill enhancement to candidates, who we think would fit a job requirement with one of o</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Hadoop-Engineer-Job-MO-US-222092223.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222092223</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 12:09:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Developer</title>
      <description>CA-San Francisco, Stefanini is looking for a Big Data Developer in San Francisco, CA. Stefanini is looking for a Big Data Engineer to join the Advanced Data and Analytics Capabilities Team. We are a team based out of San Francisco that partners with business lines across the Client System to deliver big data and advanced analytics products and solutions. In this role, you will have the opportunity to contribute to </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Developer-Job-San-Francisco-CA-US-222091277.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222091277</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 11:23:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Big Data Engineer</title>
      <description>TX-Irving, Location: Remote Duration: 12+ Months AWS Big Data Engineer: Experience developing cloud-based software services and solutions Experience creating and driving large scale ETL pipelines in AWS based environment Experience with integration of data from multiple data sources Experience creating and driving large scale big data analytics pipelines Strong software development and programming skills wit</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/AWS-Big-Data-Engineer-Job-Irving-TX-US-222088891.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222088891</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 09:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Developer - II</title>
      <description>NY-Garden City, Location: Garden City, NY Description: Our client is currently seeking a Big Data Developer - II Title: Big Data Developer Location: Garden City, NY Duration: 12+ Months What you?ll be doing. You will be part of a new Data Science team, ensuring that innovation drives continuous business improvements, bringing more profitable growth and an even better customer experience. As a Data Analytics/Predi</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Developer-II-Job-Garden-City-NY-US-222084628.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222084628</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 09:08:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYSTEMS ENGINEER IV – BIG DATA DEVELOPER</title>
      <description>CO-Cherry Hills Village, Location: Cherry Hills Village, CO Description: Our client is looking for a Systems Engineer - Big Data per the following: JOB SCOPE: Primarily responsible for ongoing development of enhancements of various data reconciliation projects, centering around Java, SQL, Hive, Hadoop, and Dart. Implement critical reporting for senior leadership, and various internal clients. Splunk and SQL Developer are </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/SYSTEMS-ENGINEER-IV-–-BIG-DATA-DEVELOPER-Job-Cherry-Hills-Village-CO-US-222086377.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222086377</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 09:20:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Administrator</title>
      <description>DC-Washington, ALTA IT Services is seeking a Sr. Big Data Administrator with at least 7 years of experience. Please contact ebrient@altaits.com Hadoop Administrator Contract ​​​​​​​Washington DC Tasks: • Lead and provide technical solutions and expertise for project teams and customers • Provide daily technical support for the Building environments and Enterprise Data Platforms (EDP) • Analyze, recommend and imp</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Administrator-Job-Washington-DC-US-221174787.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221174787</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 08:33:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering Manager - Big Data</title>
      <description>CA-San Bernardino, If you are a Data Engineering Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Fortune 500 Company! What You Will Be Doing - Lead and Manage small to large IT project initiatives related to Data and Data Delivery. - Lead and Manage production applications related to Data and Data Delivery. - Prioritizes own and teams work. Anticipates consequences of actions, potential problems</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Engineering-Manager-Big-Data-Job-San-Bernardino-CA-US-222072599.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222072599</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 05:07:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Software Engineer</title>
      <description>NJ-Bedminster, There are 2 positions and they are contract-to-hire positions. Sorry, no third party candidates can be considered. Big Data Software Engineer Position will work closely with the Product owners, Architects, Dev leads, Quality Assurance leads, and Operation in Discovery teams. In addition, conduct Code reviews, design and develop critical sections. Key Roles and Responsibilities Responsible for the </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Big-Data-Software-Engineer-Job-Bedminster-NJ-US-221696794.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221696794</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sr. Big Data Engineer</title>
      <description>TX-Houston, Genuent is hiring a Sr. Big Data Engineer for our direct client in Houston, TX. Qualified candidate should send their resume (Word format) to Taylor Kast at tkast@genuent.com Sr. Big Data Engineer – Houston, TX Direct Hire *Great comp* Sr. Big Data Engineer to help manage the uninterrupted flow of information by designing and maintaining data pipelines to deliver data across our organization. This</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Sr-Big-Data-Engineer-Job-Houston-TX-US-221254736.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221254736</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sr. Java Engineer - Big Data/Cloud</title>
      <description>CA-San Mateo, Location: San Mateo, CA Description: Our client is currently seeking a Sr. Java Engineer - Big Data/Cloud to work full-time in their San Mateo, CA location. Our client is looking for intelligent and hardworking software engineers to accelerate our path towards becoming the number one Customer Data Platform. This role involves working in an agile team to build the systems that will allow our platfo</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Sr-Java-Engineer-Big-Data-Cloud-Job-San-Mateo-CA-US-221248831.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221248831</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Data Engineer - Remote</title>
      <description>CA-Pasadena, Job Title: Senior Data Engineer - Remote Job Location: REMOTE Job Duration: Direct-hire, Full-Time Requirements: Python, Big Data tools, Hadoop, Spark, AWS, Kubernetes, Docker, ETL Pipelines Must currently have or being willing/able to obtain top secret clearance TS/SCI We are a leading technology and analytics firm, merging the newest tools in AI, Machine Learning, and Big Data to provide new and</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Senior-Data-Engineer-Remote-Job-Pasadena-CA-US-222108738.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222108738</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:21:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Scala / Spark Software Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-Santa Barbara, If you are a Senior Scala / Spark Software Engineer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 1. Our company has grown 150% in the last 2 years and are continuing to grow, and well-positioned in this current climate to deliver even more value to our customers! 2. We have an amazing company culture and an awesome work environment in beautiful Santa Barbara, California. You will b</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Senior-Scala-Spark-Software-Engineer-Job-Santa-Barbara-CA-US-222108981.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">222108981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 05:25:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT - Architect/Analyst</title>
      <description>AZ-Phoenix, Architect/Analyst – 6-month Right to hire If interested in discussing this role, please call Rita 914-461-1670 or email rdelosa@contech-it.com The work is to be performed in AZ (preferred), MN or telecommute Project/Projects the candidate will be working on while on assignment are: Individual ExchangePrograms - expansion and capability enhancements In this role, you will be part of a team. The Por</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/IT-Architect-Analyst-Job-Phoenix-AZ-US-221279656.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221279656</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering</title>
      <description>MN-Eden Prairie, Description: Data Engineering PROJECT: Position will help address a spike in the data acquisition work we routinely perform on the (ODL). The spike is due to Clinical Performance (CP) needing several new Care Delivery Organizations (CDOs) data to be acquired by the end of the year. This resource will augment current staff and provide resource dedication and focus to the CP demand. IDEAL BACKGROUND</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Engineering-Job-Eden-Prairie-MN-US-221735904.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221735904</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist</title>
      <description>NC-High Point, Logistics done differently. At XPO Logistics, we invest over $450 million in technology every year so that we can continue to develop state-of-the-art solutions for our customers. As the Data Scientist, you will be responsible for developing analytical experiments in a methodical manner and regularly evaluating alternate models to support strategic initiatives and ongoing business processes. You w</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Scientist-Job-High-Point-NC-US-221273843.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221273843</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research and Development Analytical Manager</title>
      <description>TX-San Antonio, MUST BE A U.S. CITIZEN WITH A TOP SECRET SSBI SECURITY CLEARANCE Support the development of automated detection analytics on large datasets (over 1TB). Develop hypotheses about potential Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) behavior and develop testing plans to prove, disprove or modify the hypothesis. Support testing and publication of analytics for deployment. Assist in developing and implanting dat</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Research-Development-Analytical-Manager-Job-San-Antonio-TX-US-221306349.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221306349</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entry Level/ Mid Level Python Developer</title>
      <description>NY, Greetings, Hope you all are safe and doing good at whatever you have your hands on. We are hiring for multiple roles as software programmers/developers in USA in technologies like Java J2EE and Java Full stack / Mean Stack/Mern Stack developers /Big Data (Hadoop, Spark ) Data Science and Cloud Programmers (AWS and Azure). Multiple Roles (Java Developers/Python Developers/Big Data/Hadoop/AWS) Job D</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Entry-Level-Mid-Level-Python-Developer-Job-NY-US-221724754.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221724754</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>